Guide to the Kathryn Miller Papers
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Kathryn Miller Papers
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
vifgm00071
2 containers, 1.75 cubic feet (2.625 linear feet)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Material was acquired from Katryn Miller in 2005.
Biographical/Historical Information
The collection contains materials pertaining to the Loudoun Station development in Loudoun County, Virginia. Loudoun Station is a mixed-use town center development on approximately 50 acres located adjacent to the Dulles Greenway in Ashburn. It comprises office space, pedestrian-friendly retail establishments, and multi-family residences. A transit-oriented development, it will eventually combine office, residential, hotel, restaurant, retail and civic uses, all adjacent to the final METRO station on the planned extension of METRO's Silver Line.
Scope and Content
Collection details the early developing stages of the Loudoun Station project. Collection comprises correspondence, reports, zoning materials, maps, and design materials.
Arrangement
Collection is arranged according to subject.
Contents List
- Kathryn Miller (Loudoun Station)
  - Department of Building and Development, Country of Loudoun: Memorandum, Folder 1 (Box Box 1)
  - 7-21-03 Draft: Chapter 1 pp. 1 - 1241, Folder 2 (Box Box 1)
  - 7-21-03 Draft: Chapter 4, Folder 3 (Box Box 1)
  - 7-21-03 Draft: Chapter 5, Folder 4 (Box Box 1)
  - 7-21-03 Draft: Chapter 6, Folder 5 (Box Box 1)
  - Proffer Statement for Loudoun Station (Rezoning application), Folder 6 (Box Box 1)
  - Loudoun Station design guidelines and standards / Planning Commission archives, Folder 7 (Box Box 1)
  - Department of Planning Staff Report, Folder 8 (Box Box 1)
  - 7-21-03 Draft: Chapter 7, Folder 9 (Box Box 1)
  - 7-21-03 Draft: Chapter 8, Folder 10 (Box Box 1)
  - Z map 2002 - 2005 Loudoun Station (2nd referral), Folder 11 (Box Box 1)
  - Z map 2002 - 2005 (bound), Folder 12 (Box Box 1)
  - Proposed Ordinance Modifications, Folder 13 (Box Box 1)
  - Loudoun Station:Transit Oriented Development Report April 1, 2003, Folder 14 (Box Box 1)
  - Loudoun Station: Responde to 2nd OTS referral, Folder 15 (Box Box 1)
  - Demograaphics Map for Loudoun Station, Folder 16 (Box Box 1)
  - Loudoun Station Z map 2002 -2005 (powerpoint presentation) June 18, 2003, Folder 17 (Box Box 1)
  - Loudoun Station images 6/13/03 (CD): Davis, Carter, Scott Architecture and Interiors, Folder 18 (Box Box 1)
  - Loudoun Station: Comstock proposal, Folder 19 (Box Box 1)
  - Loudoun station Z map 2002 - 2005 - Wetlands Delineation, Folder 20 (Box Box 1)
  - Fiscal Impact Analysis of Loudoun Station report, Folder 21 (Box Box 1)
  - Phase I archeological investigation of a 42 Acre property on Shellhorn RD, Folder 22 (Box Box 1)
  - environmental report for zoning map amendment application, Folder 23 (Box Box 1)
  - Loudoun Station traffic impact study 1/24/02, Folder 24 (Box Box 1)
  - Loudoun Station approval documents - ZMap 2002 - 2005, Folder 1 (Box Box 2)
  - Tax map 79 Parcel {(2)} 1 + 2, Parcel 26 + 26A and ZMap 2002-2005 application, Folder 2 (Box box 2)
  - ZMap 2002 -2005 Loudoun Station - Correspondence (1 of 6), Folder 3 (Box Box 2)
  - ZMap 2002 - 2005 Loudoun Station - Correspondence (2 of 6), Folder 4 (Box Box 2)
  - ZMap 2002-2005 Loudoun Station - Correspondence (3 of 6), Folder 5 (Box Box 2)
  - Zmap 2002 - 20005 Loundoun Station - Correspondence (4 of 6), Folder 6 (Box Box 2)
  - ZMap 2002 -2005 Loudoun Station - Correspondence (5 of 6), Folder 6 (Box Box 2)
  - ZMap 2002-2005 Loundoun Station - Correspondence (6 of 6), Folder 8 (Box Box 2)
  - Loudoun Station ZMap 2002 - 2005, 1st and 2nd agency referrals, Folder 9 (Box Box 2)
  - Loudoun Station ZMap 2002 - 2005, 3rd and 4th agency referrals, Folder 10 (Box Box 2)
  - Loudoun Station ZMap 2002 -2005 - Department of Planning Staff report 6/18/03, Folder 11 (Box Box 2)
  - Loudoun Station ZMap 2002 -2005 - Department of Planning Staff Report 9/17/03, Folder 12 (Box Box 2)
  - Loudoun Station ZMap 2002 -2005 - Department of Planning Staff report 11/5/03, Folder 13 (Box Box 2)
  - Loudoun Station ZMap 2002 - 2005 - Proffer Statement Drafts (1 of 2), Folder 14 (Box Box 2)
  - Loudoun Station ZMap 2002 -2005 - Proffer Statement Draft (2 of 2), Folder 15 (Box Box 2)
  - Loudoun Station Z Map 2002 -2005 - design guidelines, draft (1 of 2), Folder 16 (Box Box 2)
  - Loudoun Station Z Map 2002 -2005 - design guideline, Draft (2 of 2), Folder 17 (Box Box 2)
  - Loudoun Station Z Map 2002 -2005 - Planning Commission and Board of Supervisors, affidavits for public hearing, Folder 18 (Box Box 2)